RELEASE STRESS
Welcome!
Stress can be related
to anxiety, worry, and pressure in life
from the heart and mind.
Release stress from your heart, mind and body
and bring peace to your heart
with love, light and nourishment
from the transformative art field
of the Tao Calligraphy Greatest Love.
Greatest Love melts all blockages
and transforms all life.
Sit up straight.
Take a deep breath.
Relax and gently focus on your heart.
STEP 1
Inhale.
Universal golden light
and the light of the moon, mountains and ocean
radiate from the Tao Calligraphy
of Greatest Love
into your first energy center
to form a golden light ball.
Exhale.
Chant
“Ah”
as the light ball rotates up to the heart
and radiates golden light
in all directions.
Ah
STEP 2
Inhale.
Universal golden light
and the light of the moon, mountains and ocean
radiate from the Tao Calligraphy
of Greatest Love
into your first energy center
to form a golden light ball.
Exhale.
Chant
“Ah, Ah, Ah”
as the light ball rotates up
to the heart
and radiates golden light
in all directions.
Ah Ah Ah
STEP 3
Put five fingertips together
to trace the Oneness path
of the Greatest Love
Tao Calligraphy
with all your heart.
Connect and receive Greatest Love
to nourish your heart
and release stress.
STEP 4
Inhale.
Universal golden light
and the light of the moon, mountains
and ocean
radiate from the Tao Calligraphy
of Greatest Love
to your heart
form a golden light ball.
Exhale.
The light ball radiates golden light
from the heart
in all directions.
Take a deep breath.
Integrate the love,
the light
and the nourishment.
How do you feel?
Less stress and more relaxed?
Repeat this meditation
anytime you feel stress coming on
or want more relaxation.